Entertainment Teach-In
It's time for the Entertainment Teach-In!
And I'm Sayu Aizawa, a voice actress.
I'm voice actress Sayu Aizawa, nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
In the Entertainment Teach-In, actors, artists, directors, and cultural figures introduce their works that they want to promote.
Actors, artists, directors, and cultural figures introduce the works they want to promote, and just have a good time chatting with each other.
The facilitator of this program is decided by rock-paper-scissors-scissors.
The winner of the rock-paper-scissors game wins.
The winner of the game will be the facilitator of today's program.
First, let's play rock-paper-scissors-scissors.
I'm Rika Mayama, the newlywed.
Aizawa-san, please introduce yourself again.
I'm Saya Aizawa, playing the role of Ayano Kimishima in “Arya next door who can sleep in Russian with a pounding voice.
I'm Saya Aizawa, playing the role of Ayano Kimishima.
And...
Yes, the morning channel has arrived, and I am Mayamarika, attendance number 3 from Ebisu Chugaku.
Next month, on August 17th and 18th, we'll be holding the Bichu Summer Family Movie, or Famiie in Yamanaka High School 2024.
We will be holding it at the Yamanaka Koryu Kouryuu Kouryuuza Kirarashi Atan Hibiki!
And as for my personal solo activities... I love anime!
So I'm going to talk about my favorite anime, “Mayamarika's Anime 300%”.
I'm going to talk about my favorite anime, “Mayamarika's Anime 300%”, which is a live broadcast program on the Nico Nico Channel service.
The service is currently suspended.
The service is currently suspended, but will be resumed from the end of April.
Yes, that's right...
Amestalou, have you always been a start-up?
Yes, in 2016, a voice actor club was established.
As a member of the first term of the club
I've been a part of the movement.
I didn't realize that.
That's right.
So you always wanted to be a voice actor?
I always wanted to be a voice actor.
And then you got a job at Stardust.
Yes.
Did you get the job at Payne?
I've been applying to a lot of places.I was actually accepted at various places
Now open auditions for voice actors
I was a high school student at the time.
Mr. Masataka Kubota happened to be at my part-time job
I wrote “Stardust Promotion” on the receipt.
I searched the office and found that the voice actor audition had just started.
So I applied.
I see.
When I was in elementary school, I wanted to be an entertainer after reading an audition magazine.
And then I found Stardust Promotion, and I saw the name of Kenko Kitagawa and Yui.
Yui's name was there.
Yui's name was there?
So I applied for the job. I thought I was going to be an actress, but before I knew it, I was an idol.
So you wanted to be an actress first?
But then I realized I've been an idol for a long time.
Last year, I was in an animated film called “Who said death is beautiful?
It was Japan's first animated film made with AI.
Every time I do postrecording, I think to myself
It was difficult for me to act with just this. I was impressed by voice actors once again.
I was impressed by the voice actors again.
I've done a few performances on stage, but when they make me stand up and say my lines...
I was wondering where I should go and how to move my body.
It's the complete opposite of what I usually do.
I move my body and dance.
I tend to express myself in the lyrics.
I'm very good at putting emotion into lyrics.
I feel that I am very good at it.
Do you tend to do postrecording without moving your body?
I move.
The sound of the paper and the paper matches take over.
Yes, I try not to make noise.
And the risers don't move either? I'm told I move a lot.
Oh, you don't move? But, you know, there are many people.
Yes, there are.
I found one more thing in common on wikipedia.
What's that?
Do you like the number of times you've seen me with a camera?
Yes, I do. Oh, I like it.
I like it too, and I'm a royal.
Oh!
There's a voice actress, Yukari Tamura.
She's really cute.
Her twin-tail hair fits her well, and she sings very well.
She has a wonderful voice.
Do you have a favorite character that she has played?
You have played hundreds of characters.
From the ones who live in the daytime...
Ah! Rika-chan!
Rika... well, I played her in the remake.
I played her in the remake.
I like characters with a dark side.
I like characters with darkness in them.
I'm trying to bring out that darkness.
I see.
Now then, I would like to introduce some of my works that we would like to promote to each other.
First of all, let's start with Marino Hagen, who sometimes blurts out in Russian.
Marino Hagen, who sometimes blurts out in Russian.
Yes, I'm Marino Hagen.
The title already says it all.
The charm of the work is that there is a beautiful Russian girl sitting next to me,
That girl,
I don't want her.
I don't understand.
But actually, the girl sitting next to me can hear me.
What?
Because of what you say?
That's right.
In Russian, the word “milanska” means “cute,” but I don't think Arya realizes it, so she says things like “milanska,” “cute,” and “you have this part.
In fact, she is quite outspoken about it.
But she pretends she doesn't know. The boy child understands.
They understand, but when I ask them what they said, they say, “I said idiot.
They say something completely different. You say totally different things.
In tsun-tele, you say “roshidere,” which is a new Russian word for terere.
Again, something different from tsun-tele.
It's true, because you can hear the whole thing.
If only I could understand Russian.
I play the role of Yuki, a character named Suwar Yuki.
- You play the role of Sun Tsutomu, right? Yes. - I play the role of Sun Yat-sen, the young lady.
I play the role of a young lady, Sun Catsumi, who moves around and never wavers as a follower.
She is a character called “Yuki”.
Despite the fact that the title of the anime says I can blurt out in Russian
I'm not sold on my character at all.
Sometimes I blurt out my true feelings
Or the cute smile I sometimes show.
It's called a coup de grâce.
There is none of that.
But you don't have any.
That's right.
That's what makes it so difficult.
I see.
Since the audition.
You're very sensitive.
If you show too much emotion... or too little, then...
If you don't show your emotions too much, then you become an AI, or you lose your human touch.
I'm a human being.
It was difficult to make sure that I didn't overdo it.
On the contrary, it was difficult.
It's true that in some anime, like romantic comedies, the heroines are all in there somewhere.
I think that's the theory, but they don't appear in the story.
I watched the first episode yesterday.
I'm glad I watched the first episode yesterday, and I was wondering if you'd be in it. I was wondering if it was going to be on.
I'm glad I watched the first episode yesterday, and I was wondering if it would come out, but it hasn't yet.
It's not just a romantic comedy.
There's also a bit of a serious part where the student council gets involved, and she'll be very important in the second half of the show.
I'm looking forward to seeing what's next for Ayano Kimishima.
I'm sorry, but I'm going to be greedy and introduce two of them.
First of all, I'd like to talk about Rika Mayama's Anime 300%.
I'm sorry, I'm a little greedy, but I'd like to make two introductions.
I'm doing a show on the Nico Nico Channel, and it's a pay TV showI have a show on the Nico Nico Channel, and it's a paid program.
I talk about my favorite anime as much as I want.
I have one guest per month and one guest per month.
So far, I've had a guest who is a voice actor or an animation director.
Some of them are voice actors, some are animation directors, etc.
Also, we've had idols who like anime.
We're planning to invite idols who like anime.
and ask them what they want to hear.
It's a show where you can listen to what you want to hear.
So it's not tied to a particular “cool” season, but you can listen to your favorite anime whenever you want?
Yes, it's cool.
In the guest show, I talk about whatever anime I like, regardless of the season.
And we also have a monthly “Yuru delivery”.
I call them “aristocrats” on Nico Nico Nico.
I call them “aristocrats” on Nico Nico Nico, and I'm going to share my own device of “Futamado” with them.
I had them prepare the video on their own devices.
I put my computer in front of you.
I'll put my computer in front of you, and we'll watch the anime together.
There are times when we watch anime together.
We watch anime as we like.
300%.
I'd really like you to come, Mr. Aizawa.
There are so many things I want to ask you.
I'd love to hear about your other works as well.
May I? Manager, let's keep it on the schedule today.
Okay, I know you're busy, but let's do it today.
And the family that holds the Ebichu summer family production...
This is Ebichu's annual summer concert.
Every year, we use water for the performance.
Oh, it's amazing!
It's amazing!
We use 30 tons of water.
Everyone enjoys the music of Ebichu while crying together.
It's great, it's in the summer.
That's right, we're going to hold it again this year at Lake Yamanaka.
Because it's summer, people want to get wet, don't they?
It's nice to get wet.
Lake Yamanakako is a relatively uncultivated area. Lake Yamanakako is a relatively seeded area.
That's why there are parks.
Yes, sir.
It's fine in the daytime, but at night it's very cold.
What should we do?
So, if you come to the park, please bring something to wrap yourself in.
So that's the character of Pavieng, isn't it?
It's fun to see the video without being too much at odds with each other.
During the live performance
It's very warm during the show, but it gets cold the moment the show is over, so please come prepared with something to wrap yourselves in.
Is it your 15th anniversary?
Yes, it's our 15th anniversary!
Did it all happen in a blink of an eye?
It all happened in the blink of an eye!
Oh, yeah!
When I realized!
I was still in junior high school when I joined STARDUCK.
I joined in elementary school and formed Ebichu when I was in the first year of junior high school.
It's been 15 years since then, but I feel like my mental age has stopped?
Oh, junior high school!
The concept of Ebichu is to be in junior high school forever, so I think we have stopped there,
So it has been 15 years in the blink of an eye, and I feel as if I have stopped there.
It's true, but it's all thanks to our fans,
It's been fun for me to keep supporting the same thing for 15 years, as I am constantly changing and evolving, but the people who support us have no choice but to always accept that. So, I really feel that it is thanks to those who support us.
I am an idol.
I was made to be an idol. Even my spirit was made to be an idol.
You will continue to do so for the next 16 years and 20 years, right?
Yes, I hope we can be a group that lasts for 15 to 20 years.
I am glad to hear that.
And to the fans.